Guide to the Herant A. Katchadourian Papers SC0649
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Photographic slides, 1968-2002; Accession ARCH-2014-075
  - Human Sexuality (HB 10) course materials
    These lectures were never fully written out. There are brief notes written on the sides of the original slides but only some of these are reproduced here. My fragmentary lecture notes are also appended to this material. They may not be readily intelligible, (including to myself at this point). However, they may be useful in giving a general sense of my thinking in composing these lectures. The best source for complement these slides is my textbook, “Fundamentals of Human Sexuality”, Fifth Edition. Harcourt Brace, 1989.
    - Syllabus, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Lecture Notes, 1986-1998 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Listing, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Study of Sex, 1967-1999 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Anatomy, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Stimulation, 1985-2004 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Response, 1977-2004 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Hormones Development, 1978-1999 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Embryonal Development, 1978-1990 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Childbirth, 1978-1999 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Abortion, 1989-2002 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Love, 1985-1999 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Marriage and Parenthood, 1978-2004 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Evolution of Sexuality, 1973-1999 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Dev. Behav., 1971-1997 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Gender, 1974-1999 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Autoerotic Behavior, 1972-1999 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Coitus, 1971-1999 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Divorce, 1989-2002 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Casual Sex, 1977-2004 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Sexual Orientation, 1971-2004 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - STDs, 1985-2002 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Dysfunction, 1979-2005 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Pornography, 1972-1999 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Paraphilia, 1972-2004 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Sexual Aggression, 1976-2002 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Sex in Western Cultures, 1972-1999 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Cross-Cultural, 1973-2000 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Digital copies, 19937.28 megabyte(s); (4375 computer file(s) (JPG))
      - Human Sexuality (HB 10) Slides, undated; 1 flash drive(s) (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - Human Sexuality addenda (HB 10), undated; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD-R) (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Human Sexuality addenda 1 (HB 10), 2013 Nov.-Dec.; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD-R) (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Human Sexuality addenda 2-3 (HB 10), 2013 Dec.; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD-R) (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Longitudinal Study for the Class of 1981, 1978-1994 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Additional Papers, Accession ARCH-2017-065
  - Human Bio 10: Human Sexuality (Student Evaluations), 1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Human Sexuality Class (Evaluations by Female Students), 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Human Sexuality Class (Evaluations by Male Students), 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Human Biology 3A/3B Syllabus, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 4)